import "questions.dart";

List<Question> q = [
  Question(
    questionText: 'what is MY favourite color?',
    options: ['Blue', 'Green', 'Cyan', 'How would I know'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  ),
  Question(
    questionText: 'What is the capital of France?',
    options: ['New Delhi', 'Old Delhi', 'New York', 'Pris'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  ),
  Question(
    questionText: 'How many shirts are you currently wearing?',
    options: ['Zero', 'Four', 'Two', 'One'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  ),
  Question(
    questionText: 'which of these characters have pink hair?',
    options: ['Nadeshiko', 'Hitori Gotoh', 'Kirby', 'all of them'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  ),
  Question(
    questionText: 'How many Pokemons are there in gen1?',
    options: ['153', '152', '151', '150'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  ),
  Question(
    questionText: 'Bulbasaur is a...',
    options: [
      'Fire type',
      'Grass type',
      'steel type',
      'Ground type',
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  ),
  Question(
    questionText: 'Dragon type pokemons are weak to which of these types?',
    options: ['Ice', 'Dragon', 'Both', 'None'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  ),
  Question(
    questionText: 'How much damage does a super effective move does to a pokemon?',
    options: ['2x', '3x', '4x', '2x or 4x'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  ),
  Question(
    questionText: 'How many evolutions does Eevee have?',
    options: ['9', '8', '6', '3'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  ),
  Question(
    questionText: 'Who is the Champion of Unova Region in the games Pokemon Black and White?',
    options: ['Hilda', 'Elesa', 'Iris', 'skyla'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  ),
];